blockdos.net 2018-04-03

# Privacy Policy - BlockDOS

#### Information we collect

The information collected by BlockDOS includes your name, email address, contact number and IP address. To ensure the online security of our valued clients, BlockDOS uses most advanced and highly-secured technologies such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Software which encrypts any information the customer puts in during transmission.

#### How we make use of this information

We may use your email or mailing addresses for answering your comments and queries etc. Our customers may also receive newsletter or other promotional letters regarding our company and its services. BlockDOS may also use the collected information to improve its website layout, design and the purchasing experience of all its clients. We may use IP addresses to gather broad demographic information about users for instance their location and Internet service providers.

#### Our loyalty to your information security

All Personal information of our clients will NOT be released or sold to third parties under any circumstances. All the information, provided by our clients, is highly secure and protected. BlockDOS uses almost all acceptable methods to ensure protection of your personal information. We never store or misuse any financial information such as Pay Pal account details or credit card numbers by any means. We never sell or rent out the information provided to us by our clients.

#### Announcement to changes

Whenever we make a decision to change privacy policy of our company, we will post those changes in the homepage, policy statement, and other sections of the site we deem appropriate. This will keep our users informed about what information we usually collect from the users, how we use it and under what circumstances, when required by law, we disclose such information. Additionally, BlockDOS reserves the right to make any modification in its privacy statement at any time, so users are requested to review it regularly on our website. If BlockDOS makes material changes to its privacy policy, users will be duly notified by email, or through a notice posted on our homepage of the website.
